We just cut, on our jeans, we cut the whole waistline out.
Didn't undo the belt loops yet.
I'm going to undo just the bottom of the belt loops for now.
We'll do that the same way.
We're going to keep the belt loops because we're going to re-put those on for the last step.
With your knife, take the bottom of all of them, and the belt loops... they're really kind of tricky so you've got to be really kind of careful.
Just try to pry it a little at a time with the razor blade.
You want to do this to every single one of them.
There we go, so we've got one side all the way out.
Then turn it back over so you can do the other side.
Okay, we're going to want to do that to every single belt loop.
Try to keep this part of the belt loop on if you cut above this when you try to put a belt through it when you reattach it, it's not going to fit.
So, go ahead and undo all your belt loops and we'll move on to the next step.